Werner, Alfred; Papers ger096
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Writings: Articles on Artists, 1903-1979; Undated; 5
  - Turner, Joseph Mallord William. Typescripts, notes, clippings, 1964-1966; Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 39)
  - U- Artists. Clippings on artists, no writings by Werner present in the collection, Undated (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 40)
  - Ury, Lesser. Correspondence re: research on Lesser Ury, 1970-1972 (Box 14 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 41)
  - Ury, Lesser. Transcripts of articles and lectures, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 1)
  - Ury, Lesser. Notes, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 2)
  - Ury, Lesser. Clippings, student paper, photographs, 1903-1974 (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 3)
  - V- Artists. Clippings on artists, no writings by Werner present in the collection, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 4)
  - Valadon, Suzanne. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 5)
  - Valiquette. Typescript, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 6)
  - Van Borck. Notes, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 7)
  - Van Dongen, Kees. Typescript, clipping, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 8)
  - Van Gogh, Vincent. Transcripts, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 9)
  - Van Gogh, Vincent. Notes, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 10)
  - Van Gogh, Vincent. Clippings, catalogs, 1950-1968 (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 11)
  - Vasari, Giorgio. Typescript, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 12)
  - Vincent, Eva. Typescript, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 13)
  - Viollet-le-Duc, Eugene. Typescript, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 14)
  - Vollard, Ambroise. Typescript, notes, clippings, 1923-1977 (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 15)
  - W- Artists. Clippings on artists, no writings by Werner present in the collection, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 16)
  - Waldmueller, Ferdinand Georg. Typescripts, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 17)
  - Walkowitz, Abraham, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 18)
  - Walkowitz, Abraham. Clippings, 1937-1974 (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 19)
  - Wassermann, Jacob. Typescript, published articles by Werner, notes, clipping, 1953 (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 20)
  - Weintraub, William. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 21)
  - Werner, Nat. Typescript, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 22)
  - Weyden, Rogier van der. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 23)
  - Whistler, James Abbott McNeil. Typescripts, notes, clippings, 1960-1968; Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 24)
  - Woefflin, Heinrich. Typescripts, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 25)
  - Woefflin, Heinrich. Notes, clippings, photographs, 1903-1952 (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 26)
  - Woeller, Wilhelm. Typescript, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 27)
  - Wols [Alfred Otto Wolfgang Schulze]. Typescript, clipping, 1965; Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 28)
  - Wood, Grant. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 29)
  - Wright, Frank Lloyd. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 30)
  - Wright, Joseph. Typescript (review), Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 31)
  - Wunderlich, Paul. Typescripts, notes, catalogs, clippings, 1960-1970; Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 32)
  - Wyeth, Andrew and N.C. Typescripts, clipping, 1976; Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 33)
  - Y − Artists. Clippings on artists, no writings by Werner present in the collection, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 34)
  - Z − Artists. Clippings on artists, no writings by Werner present in the collection, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 35)
  - Zadkine, Ossip. Typescripts, notes, clippings, 1958-1972 (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 36)
  - Zilzer, Gyula. Typescript, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 37)
  - Zorach, William. Typescripts, notes, clippings, catalogs, 1955-1969 (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 38)
  - Zucker, Jacques. Typescripts, clipping, catalog, 1948-1955; Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 39)
  - Zvi. Typescript, Undated (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 40)
  - Zweig, Stefan. Typescript, published articles by Werner, notes, clippings, 1948-1952 (Box 15 (5-Writings: Articles on Artists), Folder 41)
- Writings: Articles on Art Topics, 1921-1978; Undated; 6
  TThis series contains typescripts, proofs, handwritten and typed notes, a small amount of correspondence, clippings, exhibition catalogs, and photographs pertaining to magazine and newspaper articles and book reviews written by Alfred Werner on various art topics, with an emphasis on Jewish themes. Although most of the typescripts of the articles are Undated, they range from the early 1940s until Werner's death in 1979.
  - African Art Museum. Clippings, 1977 (Box 15 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 42)
  - Albertina. Typescript, Undated (Box 15 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 43)
  - American Art. Typescripts, notes, Undated (Box 15 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 44-45)
  - American Art. Clippings, catalogs, 1938-1975 (Box 15 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 46)
  - American Jewish art, artists. Typescripts, Undated (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 1)
  - American Jewish art, artists. Notes, clippings, catalogs, 1934-1967 (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 2)
  - American painting. Notes, Undated (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 3)
  - American painting. Clippings, 1964-1974 (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 4)
  - Architecture. Brochure, 1952 (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 5)
  - Art from concentration camps. Typescripts, notes, clippings, photographs, 1978; Undated (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 6)
  - Art, general. Typescripts, Undated (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 7-8)
  - Art, general. Notes, clippings, catalogs, 1932-1975 (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 9)
  - Artists, general. Typescripts, Undated (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 10)
  - Austrian art. Typescripts, Undated (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 11)
  - Austrian art. Notes, photographs, Undated (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 12)
  - Austrian art. Clippings, catalogs, 1954-1971 (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 13)
  - Bauhaus. Notes, clippings, catalogs, 1967-1969 (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 14)
  - Beat generation, beatniks. Clippings, 1959-1960 (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 15)
  - Berlin. Typescripts, notes, clippings, 1961-1969; Undated (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 16)
  - Berlin, other German cities. Photographs, Undated (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 17)
  - Bezalel Museum. Typescripts, Undated (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 18)
  - Bezalel Museum. Notes, Undated (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 19)
  - Bezalel Museum. Clippings, catalogs, 1934-1976 (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 20)
  - Bible in art. Typescripts, Undated (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 21)
  - Bible in art. Notes, Undated (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 22)
  - Bible in art. Clippings, catalogs, photographs, 1954-1967 (Box 16 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 23)
  - Bible lands, art and archeology. Typescripts., Undated (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 1)
  - Bible lands, art and archeology. Notes, photographs, Undated (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 2)
  - Bible lands, art and archeology. Clippings, catalogs, 1948-1967 (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 3)
  - Bremen. Notes, Undated (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 4)
  - Canada. Typescripts, Undated (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 5)
  - Church architecture. Notes, Undated (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 6)
  - Church architecture. Clippings, 1954-1967 (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 7)
  - Drawings. Typescripts, notes, clippings, catalog, 1972-1978; Undated (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 8)
  - Ècole juive (Paris). Typescripts, Undated (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 9)
  - Eskimo art. Clippings, 1969 (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 10)
  - Esternach. Typescript, notes, clippings, 1967; Undated (Oversized 22, Folder 20)
  - Europe, travel. Typescripts, Undated (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 11)
  - Exhibitions, miscellaneous. Clippings, catalogs, 1967-1978 (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 12)
  - Expressionism. Typescripts, proofs, 1973; Undated (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 13)
  - Expressionism. Notes, Undated (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 14)
  - Expressionism. Clippings, catalogs, 1955-1973 (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 15)
  - Fauvism. Typescripts, notes, Undated (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 16)
  - Fauvism. Clippings, datalogs, 1940-1976 (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 17)
  - Franconia. Clippings, brochures, 1959-1967 (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 18)
  - French artists. Notes, Undated (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 19)
  - German art. Typescripts, Undated (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 20)
  - German art. Notes, Undated (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 21)
  - German art. Clippings, 1949-1977 (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 22)
  - German art – Degenerate art (Entartete Kunst). Typescripts, Undated (Box 17 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 23)
  - German art – Degenerate art (Entartete Kunst). Typescripts, Undated (Box 18 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 1)
  - German art – Degenerate art (Entartete Kunst). Notes, Undated (Box 18 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 2)
  - German art – Degenerate art (Entartete Kunst). Clippings, 1962-1974 (Box 18 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 3)
  - German art – Degenerate art (Entartete Kunst). Proofs of article by Werner, Undated (Oversized 22, Folder 21)
  - German art – 19th Century. Notes, clippings, 1936-1971 (Box 18 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 4)
  - German graphic arts. Clippings, catalogs, 1959-1967 (Box 18 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 5)
  - German museums. Typescripts, notes, 1962-1972; Undated (Box 18 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 6)
  - German museums. Clippings, catalogs, 1962-1978 (Box 18 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 7)
  - German painting. Typescript, notes, Undated (Box 18 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 8)
  - German painting. Photographs with notes, Undated (Box 18 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 9)
  - Golden Door. Typescripts, printed texts, 1977; Undated (Box 18 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 10)
  - Golden Door. Notes, clippings, 1976 (Box 18 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 11)
  - Hebrew manuscripts. Typescripts, notes, clippings, 1978 (Box 18 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 12)
  - Holland. Notes, Undated (Box 18 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 13)
  - Holocaust. Notes, clippings, 1965-1968 (Box 18 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 14)
  - Impressionists. Typescripts, notes, clippings, Undated (Box 18 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 15)
  - Israel. Typescripts, notes, Undated (Box 18 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 16)
  - Israel, general. Clippings, 1968 (Box 18 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 17)
  - Israeli art. Typescripts, Undated (Box 18 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 18-19)
  - Israeli art. Notes, clippings, 1957-1973 (Box 18 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 20-21)
  - Israeli children's art. Typescript, notes, clippings, photographs, 1958-1960 (Box 18 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 22)
  - Israeli crafts. Typescripts, notes, photograph, Undated (Box 19 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 1)
  - Israeli crafts. Clippings, 1947-1958 (Box 19 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 2)
  - Israeli museums. Notes, Undated (Box 19 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 3)
  - Israeli museums. Clippings, 1950-1969 (Box 19 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 4)
  - Israeli museums. Brochures, 1940-1968 (Box 19 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 5)
  - Jerusalem. Typescript, Undated (Box 19 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 6)
  - Jewish art. Typescripts, Undated (Box 19 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 7-8)
  - Jewish art, artists. Notes, Undated (Box 19 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 9)
  - Jewish art. Clippings, 1921-1975 (Box 19 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 10)
  - Jewish art in Britain. Typescripts, notes, Undated (Box 19 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 11)
  - Jewish art in Britain. Clippings, 1951-1974 (Box 19 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 12)
  - Jewish art in Israel. Typescript, Undated (Box 19 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 13)
  - Jewish artists in Europe. Typescripts, proofs, Undated (Box 19 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 14)
  - Jewish artists in Europe. Notes, clippings, 1950-1961 (Box 19 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 15)
  - Jews in art. Notes, Undated (Oversized 22, Folder 22)
  - Jewish Museum, NY. Correspondence, clippings, catalogs, 1945-1975 (Box 19 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 16)
  - Jewish museums. Typescripts, Undated (Box 19 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 17)
  - Jewish museums. Clippings, catalogs, 1945-1968 (Box 19 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 18)
  - Jewish ritual and folk art. Typescripts, Undated (Box 19 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 19)
  - Jewish ritual and folk art. Notes, Undated (Box 19 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 20)
  - Jewish ritual and folk art. Clippings, catalogs, 1926-1970 (Box 19 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 21)
  - Jewish travel in Europe. Notes, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 1)
  - Kunst im Widerstand (Art in the Resistance). Typescripts, notes, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 2)
  - Light. Notes, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 3)
  - Luebeck. Typescripts, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 4)
  - Manuscripts. Typescripts, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 5)
  - Martyrs, martyred artists. Typescripts, notes, clippings, 1946-1964 (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 6)
  - Mexico. Typescripts, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 7)
  - Mexico. Notes, clippings, 1954-1968 (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 8)
  - Modern art. Clippings, 1968-1977 (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 9)
  - Modern German prints. Typescripts, notes, photographs, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 10)
  - Modern sculpture. Typescript with photographs, notes, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 11)
  - Museum of Art – Ein Hod. Exhibition catalogs, 1960-1968 (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 12)
  - Museums, U.S. Typescripts, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 13)
  - Naturalism. Notes, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 14)
  - Painting of the 20th century. Notes, photographs, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 15)
  - Paris. Notes, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 16)
  - Photography. Typescripts, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 17)
  - Picasso Museum. Typescripts, notes, clippings, catalogs, 1966-1969 (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 18)
  - Post-impressionists. Typescript, notes, clipping, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 19)
  - Prints, pictures, Undated (Oversized 23, Folder 1)
  - Religion in art. Notes, clippings, 1952-1965 (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 20)
  - Roko Gallery. Typescript, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 21)
  - Romanian art. Clippings, 1965-1969 (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 22)
  - Russian art. Typescripts, notes, photographs, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 23)
  - Russian art. Clippings, catalogs, 1962-1978 (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 24)
  - Salon. Typescripts, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 25)
  - Salon. Notes, clippings, 1968; Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 26)
  - Science, technology and art. Typescript, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 27)
  - Sculpture. Typescripts, notes, clippings, 1953-1976 (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 28)
  - Shtetl. Typescripts, notes, clippings, 1962-1968 (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 29)
  - Social Realism. Typescripts, notes, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 30)
  - Spain and Portugal. Typescripts, notes, clippings, 1957-1965 (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 31)
  - Sunday artists. Typescripts, notes, clippings, 1952-1954 (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 32)
  - Surrealism. Typescripts, notes. Undated, 1967-1969 (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 33)
  - Surrealism. Photographs, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 34)
  - Synagogue architecture. Typescripts, printed article, Undated (Box 20 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 35)
  - Synagogue architecture. Clippings, 1947-1961 (Box 21 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 1)
  - Synagogues. Typescripts, notes, Undated (Box 21 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 2)
  - Synagogues, Europe. Clippings, 1926-1971 (Box 21 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 3)
  - Synagogues, synagogue art. Clippings, 1951-1967 (Box 21 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 4)
  - Venice ghetto. Notes, clippings, photographs, Undated (Box 21 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 5)
  - Vienna, general. Clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 21 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 6)
  - Vienna School of Fantastic Realism. Typescript, printed article by Werner, 1965 (Box 21 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 7)
  - Vienna School of Fantastic Realism. Clippings, catalogs, 1955-1978 (Box 21 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 8)
  - Viennese art. Typescripts, notes, Undated (Box 21 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 9)
  - Women as artists. Typescripts, Undated (Box 21 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 10)
  - Women as artists. Clippings, catalogs, 1965-1978 (Box 21 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 11)
  - Works Progress Administration. Typescripts, Undated (Box 21 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 12)
  - Yugoslavia. Typescripts, notes, Undated (Box 21 (6-Writings: Articles on Art Topics), Folder 13)
- Writings: Book Reviews, Undated; 7
  This series contains typescripts of reviews written by Werner, many of which are duplicate reviews filed under specific artists and topics. The series also contains a selection of Werner's column "Views and Visions", which appeared in the monthly magazine Art Voices.
  - Book reviews, multiple. Typescripts, Undated (Box 21 (7-Writings: Book Reviews), Folder 14-15)
  - Book reviews, A – E. Typescripts, Undated (Box 21 (7-Writings: Book Reviews), Folder 16)
  - Book reviews, F – J. Typescripts, Undated (Box 21 (7-Writings: Book Reviews), Folder 17)
  - Book reviews, K – O. Typescripts, Undated (Box 21 (7-Writings: Book Reviews), Folder 18)
  - Book reviews, P – R. Typescripts, Undated (Box 21 (7-Writings: Book Reviews), Folder 19)
  - Book reviews, S – Z. Typescripts, Undated (Box 21 (7-Writings: Book Reviews), Folder 20)
  - "Views and Visions." Book reviews. Typescripts, Undated (Box 21 (7-Writings: Book Reviews), Folder 21)
  - "Views and Visions." Reviews, other topics. Typescripts, Undated (Box 21 (7-Writings: Book Reviews), Folder 22)
- Writings: Miscellaneous, 1958-1973; Undated; 8
  - Miscellaneous typescripts, in English, Undated (Box 22 (8-Writings: Miscellaneous), Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous published articles by Werner, 1958-1973 (Box 22 (8-Writings: Miscellaneous), Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous notes, Undated (Box 22 (8-Writings: Miscellaneous), Folder 3-5)
  - Bibliography of artists, art topics, A – D, Undated (Box 22 (8-Writings: Miscellaneous), Folder 6)
  - Bibliography of artists, art topics, E – J, Undated (Box 22 (8-Writings: Miscellaneous), Folder 7)
  - Bibliography of artists, art topics, K – O, Undated (Box 22 (8-Writings: Miscellaneous), Folder 8)
  - Bibliography of artists, art topics, P – Z, Undated (Box 22 (8-Writings: Miscellaneous), Folder 9)